<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Paul's Little Website</title><link>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Paul's Little Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 14:21:49 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A poorly remembered anecdote about building passively safe systems provided by someone unqualified to offer it (me) to make a point</title><link>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/passive_safety/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 14:21:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/passive_safety/</guid><description>Passive Safety Hey, this is going to be fun, but you are probably wondering how much you can skip. Once you lose interest, jump down to the next section and you will be fine.
I’m going to share with you a fun (maybe?) anecdote about nuclear (fission) power. I’m not going to fact check myself and look it up because I don’t want to find out this story is wrong then need to get a new story.</description></item><item><title>Minimum Best Practices For Data Scientists Part 4</title><link>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/data_scientist_part4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 14:21:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/data_scientist_part4/</guid><description>Minimum Best Practices For Data Scientists This is part 3.4 in a series to give some guidance on milestones/goals/expectations or really just “best practices” at various levels in the data science career. For guidance on getting to the pre-Data Scientist level look here. To learn about moving up from Data Scientist to Senior Data scientist you want this link.
This is just the fourth section on this topic.</description></item><item><title>Minimum Best Practices For Data Scientists Part 3</title><link>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/data_scientist_part3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:21:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/data_scientist_part3/</guid><description>Minimum Best Practices For Data Scientists This is part 3.3 in a series to give some guidance on milestones/goals/expectations or really just “best practices” at various levels in the data science career. For guidance on getting to the pre-Data Scientist level look here. To learn about moving up from Data Scientist to Senior Data scientist you want this link.
This is just this third section on this topic.</description></item><item><title>Minimum Best Practices For Data Scientists Part 2</title><link>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/data_scientist_part2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 14:21:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/data_scientist_part2/</guid><description>Minimum Best Practices For Data Scientists This is part 3.2 in a series to give some guidance on milestones/goals/expectations or really just “best practices” at various levels in the data science career. For guidance on getting to the pre-Data Scientist level look here. To learn about moving up from Data Scientist to Senior Data scientist you want this link.
This is just the second section on this topic.</description></item><item><title>Minimum Best Practices For Data Scientists Part 1</title><link>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/data_scientist_part1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 14:21:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/data_scientist_part1/</guid><description>Minimum Best Practices For Data Scientists This is part 3.1 in a series to give some guidance on milestones/goals/expectations or really just “best practices” at various levels in the data science career. For guidance on getting to the pre-Data Scientist level look here. To learn about moving up from Data Scientist to Senior Data scientist you want this link.
This is just the first section on this topic.</description></item><item><title>Minimum Best Practices For Data Scientists Full</title><link>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/data_scientist_full/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 14:21:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://paul-brenner.github.io/posts/data_scientist_full/</guid><description>Minimum Best Practices For Data Scientists This is the full part 3 in a series to give some guidance on milestones/goals/expectations or really just “best practices” at various levels in the data science career. For guidance on getting to the pre-Data Scientist level look here. To learn about moving up from Data Scientist to Senior Data scientist you want this link. Elsewhere on the blog I&amp;rsquo;ve also split this into multiple smaller pages.</description></item></channel></rss>